University Council; Records ua100
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the University Council, 2007 October 31 - 2018 January 17; 1; 39 captures
  - University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 July 17
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pbs.twimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host abs.twimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s.pinimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mobile.twitter.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host twitter.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host plus.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host yt3.ggpht.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host r19---sn-n4v7kn7e.googlevideo.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host es.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.pt (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host kr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.se (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host sk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host dk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ar.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fi.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host chrome.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host gaming.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host it.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host au.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host tr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host co.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ro.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host za.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host id.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host gr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.de (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cz.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host hu.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host payments.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nz.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host schema.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host in.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fonts.gstatic.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host jp.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s.ytimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host uk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ru.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host br.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host no.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host accounts.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.gstatic.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host get.adobe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host dns: (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host connect.facebook.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host vine.co (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host input.name (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.addthis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host m.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host i9.ytimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.nyraen.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host meinvz.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ualbany.alpinesystemsinc.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.xing.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host staticxx.facebook.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mar.gar.in (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ct.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.adobe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host es.pn (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host citeulike.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fai.informazione.it (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ads-latest.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cbks1.googleapis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host drive.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host archive.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cdn.youvisit.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host taringa.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host vybrali.sme.sk (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host com.google.android.youtube (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host about.me (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host uqshyy.gi (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nmnathletics.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host steamcommunity.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host getpocket.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.insidelacrosse.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.informz.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.w3.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host qr-adv.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host apps.albany.edu (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host meetvibe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host smb.cdnak.dal.neulion.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host apply.commonapp.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.atmos.albany.edu (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host code.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.info (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.ualbanydining.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mts1.googleapis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.ualbanysports.com (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host alumni.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host asrc.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host atmos.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cela.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host choose.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cs.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host csda.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cwig.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host events.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host hr.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host ibl.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host illiad.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host liblogs.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host listserv.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host m.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host math.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host omega.math.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host mumford.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host nyjm.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host pdp.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host resnet.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host rit.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host rna.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host slsc.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uaems.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uapps.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host wiki.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_DELAY for host library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: BLOCK_URL meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search?(STRING_MATCH) for host meg.library.albany.edu (created 2017-05-11, last updated 2017-05-11)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/facstaff/wkidd(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/geology/theses/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL www.ctg.albany.edu/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-07-23T00:21:36Z
    end_date: 2017-07-22T17:19:10Z
    elapsed_ms: 433389662
    discovered_count: 2896967
    novel_count: 383574
    duplicate_count: 1260379
    queued_count: 1253014
    downloaded_count: 1643953
    download_failures: 389
    warc_revisit_count: 1260323
    warc_url_count: 1643823
    total_data_in_kbs: 242227760
    duplicate_bytes: 230083618880
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3691503039
    doc_rate: 3.79
    kb_rate: 558.0
  - WARC file for University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 July 17
  - University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 October 17
    crawl: 461434
    start_date: 2017-10-17T16:55:12Z
    original_start_date: 2017-10-17T16:55:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-10-22T23:32:33Z
    end_date: 2017-10-22T22:18:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 451347360
    discovered_count: 2518613
    novel_count: 189937
    duplicate_count: 1134505
    queued_count: 1194171
    downloaded_count: 1324442
    download_failures: 463
    warc_revisit_count: 1134459
    warc_url_count: 1324359
    total_data_in_kbs: 245884744
    duplicate_bytes: 241159893710
    warc_compressed_bytes: 907278439
    doc_rate: 2.93
    kb_rate: 544.0
  - WARC file for University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 October 17
  - University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 December 22
    crawl: 512297
    start_date: 2017-12-17T20:00:47Z
    original_start_date: 2017-12-17T20:00:47Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-12-23T19:36:13Z
    end_date: 2017-12-23T02:31:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 455376460
    discovered_count: 2270828
    novel_count: 193533
    duplicate_count: 949162
    queued_count: 1128133
    downloaded_count: 1142695
    download_failures: 378
    warc_revisit_count: 949103
    warc_url_count: 1142609
    total_data_in_kbs: 191757459
    duplicate_bytes: 186288881955
    warc_compressed_bytes: 356950915
    kb_rate: 421.0
  - WARC file for University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 December 22
  - University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2018 January 17
    crawl: 541502
    start_date: 2018-01-17T16:55:02Z
    original_start_date: 2018-01-17T16:55:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2018-01-23T00:58:33Z
    end_date: 2018-01-22T18:48:48Z
    elapsed_ms: 438814889
    discovered_count: 1320686
    novel_count: 427760
    duplicate_count: 675714
    queued_count: 217212
    downloaded_count: 1103474
    download_failures: 451
    warc_revisit_count: 675659
    warc_url_count: 1103350
    total_data_in_kbs: 179372053
    duplicate_bytes: 171652108423
    warc_compressed_bytes: 225491217
    kb_rate: 408.0
  - WARC file for University Council - Home - University at Albany - SUNY, 2018 January 17
- Meeting Records, 1844-2015; 2; 6.33 cubic ft. 139 Digital Files
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the minutes of the University Council and its predecessor bodies. The approved minutes of the Executive Committee, Board of Trustees, and the Board of Visitors (1844-1939, 1944-45) are supplemented by correspondence, annual budgets, and annual reports. The minutes are available in the original hand and typewritten bound volumes, 1844-1939, 1945, kept by the secretary to the various committees and boards, and a typewritten transcription, 1844-1939, commissioned by President Brubacher in 1938. No minutes exist for the College Council (1954-62), though one agenda from 1960 is in the records. The minutes of the University Council (1963-89), contain several reports and budget documents, however the bulk of the correspondence, reports, and peripheral material considered by the University Council are found in the correspondence files.
  - Annual Report of the Executive Committee of the State Normal School, 1844-1852 (Call-number SPE LD 3841 A22X)
    - Annual Report, 1844 March 22; 4.09 MB
    - Annual Report, 1845 January 31; 1.03 MB
    - Annual Report, 1846 January 27; 1.41 MB
    - Annual Report, 1847 February 5; 941.72 KB
    - Annual Report, 1848 January 13; 1.61 MB
    - Addendum Report, 1848 March 23; 303.83 KB
    - Annual Report, 1849 January 12; 1.12 MB
    - Annual Report, 1850 February 11; 1.23 MB
    - Annual Report, 1851 March 28; 777.97 KB
    - Addendum Report, 1851 January 8; 1.39 MB
    - Annual Report, 1852 January 12; 2.19 MB
    - Addendum Report, 1852 April 12; 1.94 MB
  - Annual Report of the Executive Committee of the State Normal School, 1853-1859 (Call-number SPE LD 3841 A22X)
    - Annual Report, 1853 January 17; 1.67 MB
    - Annual Report, 1854 January 14; 2.16 MB
    - Annual Report, 1855 January 19; 3.73 MB
    - Annual Report, 1856 January 22; 1.8 MB
    - Annual Report, 1857 January 21; 1.68 MB
    - Annual Report, 1858 February 4; 1.94 MB
    - Annual Report, 1859 January 19; 1.41 MB
  - Annual Report of the Executive Committee of the State Normal School, 1860-1868 (Call-number SPE LD 3841 A22X)
    - Annual Report, 1860 January 18; 1.68 MB
    - Annual Report, 1861 January 11; 1.77 MB
    - Annual Report, 1862 February 24; 2.19 MB
    - Annual Report, 1863 February 10; 2.75 MB
    - Annual Report, 1864 January 19; 2.16 MB
    - Annual Report, 1865 January 25; 2.27 MB
    - Annual Report, 1866 March 3; 3.37 MB
    - Annual Report, 1867 February 2; 2.33 MB
    - Annual Report, 1868 January 24; 1.65 MB
  - Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction and the Regents of the University, 1869-1871 (Call-number SPE LD 3841 A22X)
    - Annual Report, 1869 February 10; 1.27 MB
    - Annual Report, 1870 January 19; 1.44 MB
    - Catalogue of Graduates, 1871; 3.98 MB
  - Executive Committee Minutes (typescript), 1844-1852 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes (typescript), 1853-1868 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1869-1888 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1889-1909 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1909-1918 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1919-1923 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes (typescript), 1924-1928 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Board of Visitors Minutes, 1929 May-1939 August; 1944 October; 1945 January (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Agenda of enclosures negarelinis, New Site, Quality of Education Report, 1960 November 28 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1963 May-1974 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1965 May-1971 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1972 January-1974 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1975 January-1976 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1975 January-1977 May (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1976 January-1977 May (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1977 January-1977 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1977 August (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1977 June-1978 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1978 June-1978 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1978 January-1978 June (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1978 July-1979 May (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1979 January-1979 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Committees, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Committees, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1979 June-1980 December (Box 1 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 25)
  - Meeting, 1980 October 27 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1980 November 24 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1980 December 22 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)